<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>ilookedeverywhere</title>
    <link>www.ilookedeverywhere.com</link>
    <description>A site by ilookedeverywhere</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Elizabeth K Whitfield</copyright>
    <image>
      <title>ilookedeverywhere</title>
      <link>www.ilookedeverywhere.com</link>
      <url>/assets/images/pinksplatter_render_web.jpg</url>
      <width>500</width>
      <height>500</height>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Pink Splatter 3D</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:50:10 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0019-art-pinksplatter-3D.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes me think of the feelings of curiousity and discovery. And the possibility of magic. Sometimes I wonder if I should stop using the color pink. But then I think, I love pink. So what the heck.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink Splatter</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:49:43 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0018-art-pinksplatter.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, I was still telling myself that I was working on the 3D paint idea for CG, but I ended up making something I just liked to look at again. 🥰]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tree By The Beach</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:49:11 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0017-art-treebythebeach.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I was trying to test out making 3D paint strokes using Krita, as a test to place on a 3D model. I got distracted, and made this instead. The strokes to the right reminded me of a palm tree, and the blue in the back reminded me of water. That's why I named it "A Tree By The Beach".]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backlog End</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:48:48 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0016-ann-backlogend.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Everything before this point has been a "backlog" - pieces that I made before making this website, but I wanted to include them here. From here on, it's REALITY. If you want to follow my posts, subscribe to my RSS feed!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2P Web</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:48:13 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0015-p2pweb_1.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Why I'm excited about the p2pweb: ...]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquarius Sun</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:47:41 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0014-art-aquariussun.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sun is in aquarius, which means...]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:47:33 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0013-art-water.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's a haiku for you.....]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Excited</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:47:19 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0012-mus-imexcited.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[#music | Why was I excited? I'm not sure. Maybe because this is the first song I feel excited to have made. But that might be just me reverse projecting emotions onto it. I really don't remember! It's kind of a demo right now though, which means it isn't complete yet. Still, I hope you enjoy it.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Girl Mountain</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:46:35 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0011-art-magicgirlmountain.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sometimes, you need to make art just for yourself. Sometimes when you give yourself the least amount of pressure, you make something you really like. Who cares what other people think! I don't! That's not really related to this image, but what the heck. Love, Elli]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cups</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:43:43 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0010-art-cups.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[# art | I was trying to make one thing, but it just didn't want to be. It ended up being this instead. I rathe like it. I don't know if this process is the most frustrating or most gratifying part of making art. For me, it's to be decied...]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bday Cake</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:43:24 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>entry-pages/0008-art-bdaycake.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | This was made for my mom's birthday. Happy Birthday!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On A Stone</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 22:42:58 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>entry-pages/0007-art-onastone.html</link>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | This is a self portrait. At the time, my hair looked like that. Of course, everything else is pretty interpretive.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feminismo</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:31:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0006-art-feminismo.html</link>
      <author>elli@ilookedeverywhere.com</author>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | Feminismo means "Feminism" in spanish. It's pretty popular right now to wear plain t-shirts with just a little design on it - called "norm-core". Although I like this as an image, I think fashion can be a lot more exciting and fun and I want to push that when I make clothing in the future. However, the most important thing to me in fashion right now is sustainable practices.

I don't know how to write about this, but if you're curious I'll try to sum it up as simply as possible.... ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nicky and Sissy</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:30:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0005-art-nickysissy.html</link>
      <author>elli@ilookedeverywhere.com</author>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | A self portrait of Nicholas and I, or any two people in love.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flower</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:30:57 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0004-art-flower.html</link>
      <author>elli@ilookedeverywhere.com</author>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | The older I am, the more I appreciate and love plants. My Mom was always gardening when I was a child and I would help her. Back then, it was pretty 50/50 whether I liked doing it or not. But now, having a garden to tend like my mama did is something I dream of all the time.....]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thumbelina</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:30:52 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0003-art-thumbelina.html</link>
      <author>elli@ilookedeverywhere.com</author>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | I've always liked the idea of Thumbelina. Here, I was exploring the idea of a girl who grew up in a bottle - protected, but out of touch with the experiences she yearned for. In this image, she is looking up at the stars and holding her hand up, trying to be closer to the world outside the glass.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil Painting</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 14:28:56 -0800</pubDate>
      <link>/entry-pages/0002-art-oilpainting.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">dat://0edb9f17724c7070ae4ad4025feba9140c611d25f48eaef40917a7f93fa3c32e/entry-pages/0002-art-oilpainting.html</guid>
      <author>elli@ilookedeverywhere.com</author>
      <description><![CDATA[#art | I made this way back in either 2013 or 2014 if I remember correctly. I need to get back into oil painting, and I can feel that I will soon.]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>